There is this famous Google interview
question that everyone gets wrong.
You're shrunk down to the size of a
nickel and put into a blender. The
blades will start spinning in 60
seconds. So, what do you do?
>> I would like to think I could duck down
and miss the blades.
>> Push the button.
>> Ask nicely for the blender not to be
turned on.
>> Accept defeat. I mean, I'm the size of a
nickel. Like, what quality of life is
that?
>> That's still too big for me to quantum
tunnel or anything like that.
>> Tie my clothes together [music] and then
like use it as a rope, I guess.
>> If I was lighter, I could maybe catch a
draft up.
>> I'd say you're pretty hooped.
>> Honestly, the thing I would think about
is trying to get to the very center of
the blades. It's spinning around me, but
the actual RPM is probably not that high
if I'm standing in the middle. I time my
clothes to one of the tips of the blades
as it's starting up. Yeah, I get it to
swing me around and then I
>> But these answers don't cut it.